oncesearch.com 2006-06-14

# OnceSearch.com

                                                                                                   Oncesearch Privacy Policy

Oncesearch.com is absolutely committed to the protection of your privacy. Any information we collect, such as email addresses, is submitted at the visitor's will. We do not and will not share any personal information with any third parties unless by governmental order. 

We have no access to the information collected by the Payment Services Providers we use to payout our affiliates. These Payment Services may use cookies and/or personal information recorded from your machine (such as host,e-mail,ip,country). Follow the following links to the privacy policy's of these Payment Services Providers: 

Paypal: [ http://www.paypal.com/cgi-bin/webscr?cmd=p/gen/ua/policy_privacy-outside](http://www.paypal.com/cgi-bin/webscr?cmd=p/gen/ua/policy_privacy-outside)   
E-Gold: [ http://www.e-gold.com/unsecure/policy.htm#Privacy](http://www.e-gold.com/unsecure/policy.htm#Privacy)   
MoneyBookers: [ http://www.moneybookers.com/app/help.pl?s=privacy](http://www.moneybookers.com/app/help.pl?s=privacy)

Registration  
In order to use this Web site, you must first complete the registration form and create a user name and password. During registration you are required to give contact information (such as name and email address and postal address). We only use this information to validate your existence and to contact you when needed for the services we offer. 

Uses of Information  
Upon registration we request you to give us your full name, your country, your full telephone number and your full postal address. This information will be uses for contact purpose and user validation purpose.  
We will never give/sell/share any kind of information collected by us from the visitors on oncesearch.com.

As a listing partner, we record only IP address, country and hostname from visitors that you send to our site. If you are an xml partner we also record the username from the affiliates that send traffic to us via your engine.

Communications from the Site  
Special Offers and Updates  
We will occasionally send you information on services, special deals, promotions. 

Service-related Announcements  
We will send you strictly service-related announcements on rare occasions when it is necessary to do so. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance, we might send you an email.  
Generally, you may not opt-out of these communications, which are not promotional in nature. If you do not wish to receive them, you have the option to deactivate your account. 

Customer Service  
Based upon the personally identifiable information you provide us, we will send you a welcoming email to verify your username and password. We will also communicate with you in response to your inquiries, to provide the services you request, and to manage your account. We will communicate with you by email, in accordance with your wishes 

We do not share your profile with other third parties. Upon breach of our terms, we share your IP address with third parties. 

Information Sharing and Disclosure  
We share aggregated demographic information about our user base with our partners and advertisers. This information does not identify individual users.  
For our services that we offer, we share your country and ip address with our partners(Partners that offer us listings) for proxy,country filtering.

Personally identifiable information:  
We DO NOT Share Personally Identifiable Information with Third Parties.

Log Files  
As is true of most Web sites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data.  
We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users’ movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole.

We do not link this automatically-collected data to personally identifiable information. IP addresses are tied to personally identifiable information to protect us from fraudulent activites.

Cookies  
A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user’s computer for record-keeping purposes. We use cookies on this site. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site.  
We use session cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our site.

Some of our business partners (e.g., advertisers) use cookies on our site. We have no access to or control over these cookies. See “Third Party Advertisers.”  
This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by oncesearch.com only and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

Third Party Advertisers  
The ads appearing on this Web site are delivered to users by Google, our advertising partner. We share Web site usage information about users with reputable third party "Google" for the purpose of targeting our Internet banner advertisements on this site.

For more information about our third-party advertisers, or to learn more about the choices available to you regarding this anonymous information, please click here.

Links to Other Sites  
This Web site contains links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by oncesearch.com. Please be aware that we, oncesearch.com, are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites.  
We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information.  
This privacy statement applies only to information collected by this Web site.

Access to Personally Identifiable Information  
If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct, update, delete or deactivate it by making the change on our member information page, or by emailing our Customer Support via our online support form.

Business Transitions  
In the event oncesearch.com goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, your personally identifiable information will likely be among the assets transferred. You will be notified via prominent notice on our Web site for 30 days of any such change in ownership or control of your personal information.

Changes in this Privacy Statement  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.  
We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page.
